See you
next
time.
She jumped off the bridge!
WAIT!
It's gonna fly!
Don't follow her!
Polly!
You running down there isn't
gonna do her a lick of good.
But...
You know how dangerous it is.
You'll drown just like her.
If it gets bad, I'll handle things myself.
I wouldn't have the guts to do that.
She's either brave or stupid.
No, this is definitely
stupid. Hey! Come back! Quick!
The sea's gonna swallow you up!
A sea anemone.
a sea anemone why is a sea anemone
coming out of a chimney wait a second
No, wait!
Not the reindeer, too!
You're awesome, Pirate Lady!
Don't be a fool, girl!
You won't make it back in time!
You can see for yourself!
The wave's gonna hit any second now!
Oh, man!
There's no tuning back now!
They're as good as dead!
Saru! Hey! You okay?
Can you hear me?
Chumper!
This is it.
I can't go any further.
Luffy!
You idiot!
What the hell are you doing up there?!
Nami!
Where are you?
I can't see!
Okay! Listen! Listen!
It's not my fault!
That pigeon guy sent me flying and I got
stuck between these
buildings so I can't move!
I'm trying though!
Is this a joke to you?
We don't have time for this.
Those guys from the
government took Robin away.
And you weren't even there to help.
She did it all for us. You know.
She's going to sacrifice herself.
The government was
planning on attacking us,
but Robin turned herself over
to CP9 so we would be safe!
There's no place left in this
world for me to go or return to.
I'm afraid you're wrong.
This is the last time you'll ever see me.
She knew they would kill her.
But she didn't care.
Then Robin was lying.
This whole time.
I'm glad.
Don't worry.
I won't let Robin die!
Check out the size of that thing! Oh, man!
The waves have never been that big before!
Hey, this is really bad, guys!
Run away, pirate lady!
You gotta get out of there!
You too, reindeer!
You're gonna tear me in half!
You're really stuck!
How did you get in there
in the first place?
Who cares?
What do we do?
That wave's gonna hit any second now!
How the hell should I know?
Hold on, that's funny.
Hey, Chopper, are you
carrying the content suit?
Huh?
Your sword?
Yeah, I have one of them.
How on earth did you know that?
Well, I can tell with that one at least.
It's cursed.
Anyway, thanks for carrying it for me.
Here, quick. Put it in my hand.
Run away!
Get to higher ground, hurry!
It's all over.
They're not going to make it.
They'll get swept away for sure.
Aqua Laguna is here!
Oh, no!
Ah! They're tougher!
Whoa!
That guy's out of control!
He's knocking over buildings!
AAAAAHH!
Dial!
Stay back, Chopper!
Blunt Sword Style!
Thirty-six Kaliber Phoenix!
This is bad!
They're wrecking a town!
NAMI! Let's go!
Holy crap!
Trouble! Jumping!
Just hold on to me!
They're washing away!
Hey, look!
They made it!
I think!
It should be safe on the bridge.
Yeah, it's a big wave,
but it's not that big.
You guys are amazing!
You gotta teach me that one.
Oh, no!
The tidal wave's still
coming! Destroy! Make it?
I don't know, man.
All I can see is water.
Look! Over there!
It's Paulie!
Crap!
Hurry!
We're not safe yet!
Run to shipbuilding island!
Run for it!
Rich is done for!
I've never seen anything like that.
The waves have never
made it this far before.
I thought we'd be safe here.
Look, the tide's ebbing again.
Of course it is.
This is just the beginning.
There's going to be another wave like
that, and another after that one.
If we want to live, we've got to get
to higher ground like everyone else.
You morons.
You're lucky to be alive.
Thanks.
You saved us, rope guy.
I didn't know Aqua Laguna
would be like that.
I can't stop shaking.
If it was that bad
every year we'd be sunk.
I'm just as surprised as you folks are.
This ain't normal at all.
You pirates are one step shy of crazy.
You're lucky to be alive right now.
Oh hey monster granny.
I didn't know you were here too.
Of course I am.
I may be drunk but I'd have to Be
stupid to stay at sea during this storm.
You were awesome mr pirate.
Your arms were like boing
Yeah, I know.
I was gonna die!
Little turd.
Put my face in that death
grip and pass out like that?
Hey, Zoro.
What were you doing down
there when the wave hit?
Couldn't you get away?
Oh, yeah, you know.
Zoro got stuck in a chimney.
You got stuck in a chimney?
Zoro, you dope!
I couldn't be that lame if I tried!
Don't forget, you did
the same thing twice!
You're both dopes, okay?
Wait, where's Sanji and Uso?
Where's Sanji?
Oh yeah, there's a lot of
stuff I need to tell you.
You too, Zoro.
Things are certainly looking up for me.
Aokiji is a generous man.
Putting all those officers and all those
battleships at the tip of my fingers.
Not that I haven't earned it, though.
Under my fine leadership, CV9 has certainly
accomplished some excellent results?
Now, aren't you happy for
your master, Funkfreed?
But no accolade is too great
for the team who captured
Nico Robin she's been a
stain on the pride of the
government for 20 years now
and speaking of stains now
that I know that detestable
Cutty Flam is still alive I can
have the satisfaction of
making him suffer only two
people in this wide world have
the means of reviving Pluton
and both have been nicely
gathered together and let me
tell you fuck freed that train
can't get here quick enough
Soon I'll have enough power to
bring the whole world to its knees
Only one thing to do
We set off and rescue them right away
I had a feeling you'd say that
Hey help us out rope guy
We need a boat
Actually we need a Sea Train Do
you have another one of those?
There is no other Sea Train.
The Puffing Tom is one of a kind.
The man who made that train's a legend.
It's a miracle it got finished it all.
So sorry.
I can't pull another
Sea Train out of my ass.
Okay, then lend us a ship.
the strongest and fastest
one you guys have got.
Damn it, would you give it a rest already?
Are you stupid?
You saw what just happened.
You barely survived that wave on
land and you want to go out to sea?
I don't care how good the ship is.
You wouldn't last five minutes.
You idiot.
Even during a normal aqua laguna, no
ship has ever made it through the storm.
And this year, it's anything but normal.
Just look at what happened
to the back streets.
This is the first time the waves
have ever done damage like that.
Water 7 was built to last.
If it starts shaking, then
we damn well better listen.
I'm telling you,
even if you went out there in our biggest
galleon, you'd be smashed to smithereens.
I'm not going to let you sail out there
if I know you won't make it back alive.
Wait till morning.
We'll lend you a ship as
soon as the storm passes.
The rest of you head to
the evacuation shelter.
We're done searching for missing people.
Hold on. Huh?
If we wait until after the storm settles,
we won't make it in time
to save Robin, will we?
I heard about Eni's Lobby
long before we came here.
When you said it was a government
island, it made me remember something.
It's not just a base.
It's also where the Gates of
Justice are located, isn't it?
Gates of Justice?
Eni's Lobby is known as a
judicial island, but that's a lie.
The court they have
there is only for show.
The truth is, if you've been taken there,
then you're already considered guilty.
When you arrive,
the government walks you
through an empty courtroom,
leading to a pair of cold steel doors
that tower above the entire island.
Those doors are known
as the Gates of Justice.
The criminals who walk through
them must abandon all hope.
Once they reach the other side, they'll
never see the light of day again.
Once you set sail beyond those doors, there
are only two destinations you can reach,
neither of which you are
ever likely to leave.
One is Navy Headquarters,
where the strongest military powers in
the world gather in the name of justice.
The other is Impel Down,
an underwater prison filled with
torture chambers and execution blocks.
No matter how vicious they may be,
the criminals imprisoned
there can only wait for death.
In other words, going to Innie's lobby
is no different than a death sentence.
There's no trial, no justice,
and no hope of escape.
Am I right?
Robin has a bounty on her head.
No matter where they take her,
she'll face death or worse.
Every second we sit here talking, she gets
one step closer to the Gates of Justice.
Don't you dare tell us
to wait until tomorrow!
If you know that much already
I've only got one thing
to say even if the sea
was calm and you were able
to set sail that's the
last place you should ever
go don't forget you people
are wanted criminals just
the same as your friend
just like you said Hennie's
lobby is the front door
to the world government's
own personal playground
they've drawn battle lines
around that place that
should never ever be crossed
regardless of how they
feel about their crewmates
no pirate would be stupid
enough to launch a rescue
mission there they know
what would happen picking
a fight in that place is
like declaring war on the
entire navy hey I know how
you must feel but Paulie's
right you can't leave
during Aqua Laguna anyway
you'll be dead before you
even get there there's
There's no point in throwing
your lives away over this.
Luffy?
Find them!
We'll steal the ship!
Our Gourmet is counting on us!
Don't try to get in our way!
We're leaving now!
Whoa!
Even the waves got bad!
Whoa, is he gonna fight us?
That sure was scary.
Fine then.
You wanna fight, you got it.
All of you, stop it!
Kokoro?
Stop being such a damn fool, Straw Hat.
Like it or not, Polly's right on this one.
Shut up, Granny!
It's none of your business!
You sure about that, boy?
Either way, these folks are just trying
to stop you from killing yourself.
The point is, no matter how mad you
are, no ship can handle Aqua Laguna.
Only a Sea Train made by a
legendary man stands a chance.
I know that,
but I don't have any choice since the only
Sea Train in the world
has left town already!
If you're prepared to
die, then that's fine.
Just come along with me.
We'll brave the storm on my seat train
You idiots!
Don't just stand there!
If he's not wearing a uniform,
then he must be an intruder!
Get him!
I guess playing innocent
doesn't work in here.
And here I thought I
could get out of a fight.
Oh, well.
It's not my funeral.
Sanji?
Hold it!
You think we're gonna let
you get away with that?
If you're smart.
Rats!
Wait, you didn't hijack the
C-Train just to rescue me, did you?
I don't even know what you're doing here.
Also, what's your name again?
I don't believe we've
actually met before, have we?
Are you kidding me, you jerk?
Bingo!
Transponder snails
Okay, this must be a
communications room or something.
Lucky I ran into this place so soon!
Those guys I beat up in
the last card only had a
bunch of useless crap masks
and costumes and stuff.
Anyway, now that I have this,
I can get in touch with Nami.
Let me guess, he's one of
your pirate friends, isn't he?
Ex-fred, the question is, who are you?
I'm the face of Water 7's underworld,
the ship-dismantler, Franky.
So you're the bastard
who beat up Usopp, huh?
He may be dead to me now, but he
was part of our crew back then.
How many pieces do you
want me to cut you into?
It's not like that now.
A lot of stuff's changed since then.
Hey, punk!
You're lucky I'm tied up!
Come on, man, that line's getting old.
Seriously, he's a good guy.
He saved the Mary, at least for a while.
Oh, yeah.
The Mary was...
Whoa!
Come on, buddy.
You can't get all sad and mopey on me now.
Hey, Blondie, untie me!
Pretty please!
You can spend the rest of your life in
that potato sack for all I care. Screw you!
I said pretty please.
What the hell else do you want?
Stop it!
No more fighting guys look if we
keep yelling the number eight I gotta
Captain T-bone, what are you?
Been more than eight years
since anyone set foot in
here And nobody's touched
the C-train for more than 12.
Let's go, Chopper! Right!
I'm warning you, the thing
may not run anymore. What?
You better be kidding me!
Now, now, settle down, boys.
You can run as fast as you like, but
you're not getting inside without the key.
Huh?
Now that's weird.
It's open.
Whoa! Awesome!
Check out the face!
So cool!
Unlike the puffing tom, this
one here is a crazy train.
Its name is Rocket Man.
Comes with no guarantees,
so board at your own risk.
Rocket Man!
Sounds fast!
Knight! Nyah! Nyah!
Did you have to add the face?
Don't worry, it may be
mean, but it won't bite.
Hey, look, it's Ice Pops!
Hello there, Straw Hat.
So, you're okay after all.
It seems your friend's
faith was well-founded.
I assume you brought them here, Kokoro?
The question is, what are you doing here?
You've been through a lot today.
You need rest.
Well, let's just say you and I
were thinking the same thing.
We have a soft spot for idiots, don't we?
Go ahead.
I just finished servicing it.
Water and coal have been loaded
and the steam's building up now.
Thanks for getting it ready for us.
We owe you one.
I wouldn't celebrate yet if I were you.
You might not even survive the ride.
This was our failed prototype
before we made the Puffing Tom.
No matter how you tune it,
you can't control its speed.
In other words, it's a runaway train.
That's fine.
It can go as fast as it wants.
Hurry up! Let's go!
Get on already!
We're leaving as soon as
Nami gets here, Granny!
Oh, man!
Luffy, are you okay?
You've been kind of shaky on
your feet since we found you.
He probably just lost too much blood.
Maybe.
I am feeling kind of dizzy.
I think I need some meat.
Hurry, this way!
Wait!
I don't see why you have to go all the
way down here just to eat your dinner!
That's right!
If you're hungry, eat now!
You think all that food is for me?
What?
Sorry I took so long! Nami. Hey!
Save the small talk for later!
Get on board so we can go!
Wow, amazing.
So there's another Sea Train, huh?
He was hiding here all this
time, and we never knew.
This is a real surprise.
You're the one who told
us we have to hurry.
Why are you the last one to get here?
And what's with the big bag?
I brought you food and drinks.
I'm sorry I just yelled at you.
He's ready to go.
You'll shoot out of the
canal into the ocean.
If you can latch onto the railway
after that, it should be a good start.
Don't you worry a bit.
I like to drink, but I
take my job seriously.
You just stay here and give
that body of yours a good rest.
Sounds fine to me.
And while I'm taking care
of these pirate folk,
I hope you don't mind watching
Gonbe and Jimny for me.
Huh?
Straw Hat!
Who there?
The Franky family!
We're kind of busy right now.
Please, Straw Hat!
You guys gotta take us with you.
The people from Galley-La said you
were gonna take a CK to Enies Lobby?
Those government bastards took Franky.
They took our bro away from us.
We wanna go but we can't get
through Aqua Laguna alone.
You sure you wanna pick
a fight on their turf?
I'll fight anyone anywhere.
We gotta get our bro back.
I don't care what happens to
us as long as we can save him!
We're begging you?
Please help us, Straw Hat!
We'll do anything!
If we don't hurry, bro is done for!
You've gotta be kidding me!
You steal our money, beat up our
friend, then ask us for help?
I don't care!
Even if it's wrong, I'm still begging you!
I'll give up my pride if I can save him!
Come on. Huh?
Hurry up!
Thank you so much!
Are you sure about this?
Eh, it's fine.
Thank you!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Well, let's go!
We don't have to get on the train, though!
We'll just hop on our king bulls and head
out to sea the same time
the train takes off!
All you gotta do is let the
bulls catch a ride on your tail!
What are king bulls?
Anyway, we're off! Thanks! See you soon!
Let's go!
Let's show those masters what
we're made of and save our bro!
How's that?
Good!
Now, let's take off.
Oh, my God.
All right, boys and girls, hold
on tight so it won't fall off.
Now to Porting Water 7 for Indy's
Lobby, here comes Rocketman!
Yeah, full speed!
Let's go!
We'll get it all back!